Where Pride Began
Stonewall is a drama, history film directed by Roland Emmerich.
Kicked out by his parents, a gay teenager leaves small-town Indiana for New York's Greenwich Village,
where growing discrimination against the gay community leads to riots on June 28, 1969.
Danny Winters, played by Jeremy Irvine.
Ray / Ramona, played by Jonny Beauchamp.
Phoebe Winters, played by Joey King.
Orphan Annie, played by Caleb Landry Jones.
Dep. Seymour Pine, played by Matt Craven.
Coach Winters, played by David Cubitt.
Stonewall is a 2015 American coming-of-age drama film directed by Roland Emmerich, written by Jon Robin Baitz, and starring
Jeremy Irvine, Jonny Beauchamp, Joey King, Caleb Landry Jones, Matt Craven, Jonathan Rhys Meyers, and Ron Perlman.
The film is set in and around the 1969 Stonewall riots, a violent clash with
police that sparked the gay liberation movement in New York City.
Released on September 25, 2015, by Roadside Attractions,
it received largely negative reviews.
The film explores themes of new york city, alternate
history, lgbt, stonewall riot, taunting.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.